JASON NAN

Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada irismgmt112@gmail.com

Dedicated, passionate, self-motivated web3 developer and quick learner as well.
4+ years of experience gives me a lot of web3 skills that I believe make me best suited for the job position that is being offered as a web3 developer including De-Fi and NFT marketplaces. I'm already ready to take up new upcoming challenges on the work front.

EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2022

WEB & BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, STURDY

- Created the upgradable vaults and liquidity pools by using Aave, Lido, Convex, Curve on Ethereum.
- Ensured the safety of smart contracts.
- Enhanced the frontend UI based on MVVM, FLUX with Context API by using React.js, Web3.js, GraphQL.
- Implemented the connecting various wallet including Metamask, Coinbase, Wallet Connect, Unstoppable Domains.
- Built the liquidation bot and monitoring tool by using Defender, Tenderly, Forta.
- Registered to Debank, Defilama.

- Key achievement:

- First lending protocol with zero-interest loans
- 3 Audits from Certik, Code4rena, Quantstamp
- Liquidity pools sharing with Balancer, Yearn
- TVL 25M+
- Reduced the web page load times by approximately 75%

2020 - 2021

WEB & BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, SPARKLESNFT

- Constructed the NFT marketplace's contracts on Songbird.
- Implemented 3 main types of trading (normal, offer, auction) for ERC721, ERC1155.
- IPFS storage for content upload.
- Enhanced the new version of frontend UI based on MVVM, FLUX by using React.js, Redux.

- Key achievement:

- First NFT marketplace on Songbird, competitive with Opensea.io
- Total trading volume is 50M+

2019 - 2020

WEB & BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, DECENTRAL.GAMES

- Created the smart contracts on Polygon(Matic) and Ethereum based on game logic including farming and staking.
- Launched the frontend UI by using React.js, web3.js which interacts with Ethereum and Polygon.
- Constructed the backend server which should process the game events from smart contract and notify to frontend via websocket.

- Key achievement:

- First community-owned casino ecosystem
- A novel meta-transactional architecture to deliver seamless, signatureless, and free in game transactions

2018 - 2019

WEB & BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, DEFIAT

- Optimized MongoDB queries for the heavy-load parts of the Node.js backend system
- Enhanced the smart contracts for farming new features using the Solidity and test scripts for the smart contracts using the truffle framework.

- Key achievement:

Improved the website responsiveness and reduced the database costs by 20%

EDUCATION

2011 - 2013

MASTER OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, LIAONING TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

• Structure of the networking system

2007 - 2011

BARCHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS, LIAONING TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

- Structure of the networking system
- Cyber security
- Web development

SKILLS

- Solidity, Rust(C/C++)
- Javascript, React.js, Web3.js, Ethers.js, GraphQL

- Node.js
- MySQL, Postgresql, MongoDB
- Networking, Linux

HOBBIES

Table Tennis

Football